Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-219)
  - Mr. President, Stage, 1962
    - Scores and parts
      - Vignette E-Russian vignette
        - Full score #23; [2] p. (Box-folder 20/8)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/14)
      - Vignette F-Washington vignette
        - Full score #19; [3] p. (Box-folder 20/9)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/15)
      - Vignette G
        - Full score, change #33; [2] p. (Box-folder 20/10)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/16)
      - Vignette H
        - Full score, change #34; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/11)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/17)
      - Vignette J
        - Full score #63A; [2] p. (Box-folder 20/12)
        - Orchestral parts (out of show?) (Box-folder 150/18)
      - Vignette K
        - Full score #63B; [2] p. (Box-folder 20/13)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/19)
      - Why shouldn't I like me? see Non-show music
      - The Washington twist
        - Full scores
          - Opening twist #2; [8] p. (Box-folder 20/14)
          - #11, dance #51; [32] p. (Box-folder 20/15)
          - New; p. 10-20 (Box-folder 20/16)
          - New #47; 14 p. (Box-folder 20/17)
          - Dance, changes; 9 p. (Box-folder 20/18)
          - Reprise #51, reprise/dance new key; [4, 6] p. (Box-folder 20/19)
          - Reprise/dance, new #51; 4 p. (Box-folder 20/20)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. each, 2, verse only (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. each, 5, chorus and patter only (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Sheet music (Box-folder 141/14)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/20)
        - New orchestral parts (Box-folder 150/21)
        - Old material? orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/1)
        - New, revised orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/2)
        - Opening twist orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/3)
        - New Washington twist orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/4)
        - Leslie orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/5)
        - Reprise orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/6)
        - New, reprise orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/7)
        - Reprise, dance orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/8)
      - Who would have thought see Pigtails and freckles
      - You need a hobby
        - Full score #48; [13] p. (Box-folder 20/21)
        - Dance (version A) full score #48; 20 p. (Box-folder 20/22)
        - Dance (version B) full score #48; [18] p. (Box-folder 20/23)
        - Ending full score #48; 2 p. (Box-folder 20/24)
        - Copyist manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 141/15)
        - Printed manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 141/15)
        - Printed piano-vocal score; p. 4-7 (Box-folder 141/15)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 141/15)
        - Orchestral parts (Box-folder 151/9)
        - Dance (old) orchestral parts (Box-folder 152/1)
        - Dance (new) orchestral parts (Box-folder 152/2)
      - Unidentified incidental music; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/25)
      - Unidentified sketches; [4] leaves (Box-folder 141/16)
      - Unidentified holograph lyrics; [1] leaf, On cardboard (Box-folder 141/16)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [23] leaves, Taped together (Box-folder 141/16)
      - Manuscript and photocopies of sketches and scores; [87] leaves, On cover: J.B. (Jay Blackton, conductor) original material? (Box-folder 142/1)
      - Manuscript and photocopies of sketches and scores for cue music; [35] leaves, On cover: Phil Lang (Box-folder 142/2)
      - Miscellaneous manuscript and photocopies of sketches and scores; [20] leaves (Box-folder 142/3)
      - Unidentified incidental music orchestral parts (Box-folder 152/3)
      - Unidentified orchestra pasteovers (Box-folder 152/4)
      - Orchestral parts: individual books for instrument/conductors
        - Conductor's original production parts (Box-folder 152/5)
        - Rehearsal piano original parts (Box-folder 153/1)
        - Violin B-2 original parts (Box-folder 153/2)
        - Conductor's original part folder, Folder only (Box-folder 153/3)
        - Reed 4 original part folder, Folder only (Box-folder 153/3)
        - Conductor cue music/lead sheets, found together in folder (Box-folder 154/1)
        - Reed 1 (Box-folder 154/2)
        - Reed 2 (Box-folder 154/3)
        - Reed 3 (Box-folder 154/4)
        - Reed 3-inserts (Box-folder 154/5)
        - Reed 5 (Box-folder 155/1)
        - Reed 6 (Box-folder 155/2)
        - Horn (Box-folder 155/3)
        - Trumpet 1-2 (Box-folder 155/4)
        - Trumpet 3 (Box-folder 155/5)
        - Trombone 1 (Box-folder 155/6)
        - Trombone 2 (Box-folder 156/1)
        - Guitar (Box-folder 156/2)
        - Harp (Box-folder 156/3)
        - Piano (extras) (Box-folder 156/4)
        - Drums (Box-folder 156/5)
        - Violin A (Box-folder 156/6)
        - Violin A2 (Box-folder 157/1)
        - Violin B1 (Box-folder 157/2)
        - Violin B2 (Box-folder 157/3)
        - Viola (Box-folder 157/4)
        - Cello (Box-folder 157/5)
        - Bass (Box-folder 158/1)
        - Recording
          - Conductor (Box-folder 158/2)
          - Reed 1 (Box-folder 158/3)
          - Reed 2 (Box-folder 158/3)
          - Reed 3 (Box-folder 158/3)
          - Reed 4 (Box-folder 158/4)
          - Reed 5 (Box-folder 158/4)
          - Trumpet 1-2 (Box-folder 158/5)
          - Trumpet 3 (Box-folder 158/5)
          - Trombone 1 (Box-folder 158/5)
          - Trombone 2 (Box-folder 158/5)
          - Harp (Box-folder 158/6)
          - Guitar (Box-folder 158/6)
          - Piano (Box-folder 158/6)
          - Percussion 1 (Box-folder 158/6)
          - Percussion 2 (Box-folder 158/6)
          - Drums 2 (Box-folder 158/7)
          - Violin A3 (Box-folder 158/8)
          - Violin A4 (Box-folder 159/1)
          - Violin B3 (Box-folder 159/2)
          - Violin B4 (Box-folder 159/3)
          - Viola 2 (Box-folder 159/4)
          - Viola 3 (Box-folder 159/5)
          - Cello 2 (Box-folder 160/1)
          - Cello 3 (Box-folder 160/2)
          - Violin A1 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin A2 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin A3 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin A4 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin B1 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin B2 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Violin B3 (Box-folder 160/3)
          - Viola 1 (Box-folder 160/4)
          - Viola 2 (Box-folder 160/4)
          - Viola 3 (Box-folder 160/4)
          - Cello 1 (Box-folder 160/4)
          - Cello 3 (Box-folder 160/4)
          - Bass (Box-folder 160/4)
        - Selections
          - Copyist’s manuscript of conductor lead sheets (piano sketch masters) (Box-folder 161/1)
          - Copyist's manuscript violin parts (no good?) (Box-folder 161/2)
          - Copyist's manuscript violin parts (out of show?) (Box-folder 161/3)
          - Copyist’s manuscript orchestral parts for utility numbers only (Box-folder 161/4)
          - Copyist’s manuscript orchestral parts (Box-folder 161/5)
          - Manuscript and photocopy parts for regular production and also recording (Box-folder 162/1)
          - Manuscript, photocopy, typescript and copyist’s manuscript parts, libretto sheets, and pasteovers (out of show) (Box-folder 162/2)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Manuscript conductor’s notes, orchestrator’s notes, signs, etc. (Box-folder 162/3)
          - Hand script lists of running order and typescript song lists (Box-folder 162/4)
      - Orchestral parts: individual books
        - Conductor - Act I (Jay Blackton) (Box 163A)
        - Conductor - Act II (Jay Blackton) (Box 163A)
        - Conductor (piano-assistant conductor) (Box 163B)
        - Conductor (associate-Woody Kessler) (Box 163B)
        - Trumpet 1 & 2 (Box-folder 164/1)
        - Trumpet 3 (Box-folder 164/1)
        - Trombone 1 (Box-folder 165/1)
        - Trombone 2 (Box-folder 165/1)
        - Horns 1 & 2 (Box-folder 165/1)
        - Reeds 1 (Box-folder 166/1)
        - Reeds 2 (Box-folder 166/1)
        - Reeds 3 (Box-folder 166/1)
        - Reeds 4 (Box-folder 167/1)
        - Reeds 5 (Box-folder 167/1)
        - Violin A1 (Box-folder 168/1)
        - Violin A2 (Box-folder 168/1)
        - Violin B 1 & 2 (Box-folder 168/1)
        - Viola 1 (Box-folder 169/1)
        - Cello (Box-folder 169/1)
        - Bass (Box-folder 169/1)
        - Guitar (Box-folder 170/1)
        - Percussion (Box-folder 170/1)
        - Harp (Box-folder 170/1)
    - Scripts/miscellaneous
      - Mimeograph copy of typed script; [118] p., 2 copies, blue plastic folders; On t.p.: Mr. President, reherasal version 7/2/62 (Box-folder 171/1)
      - Mimeograph copy of typed script; [131] p., Black plastic cover; On top right: p. 1 (Box-folder 171/1)
      - Typed script and carbon copies of typed script; [194] p., Unbound; At top: (revised) May 23rd, 1962 (Box-folder 171/2)
      - Typed script and carbon copies of typed script; [72] p., Unbound (Box-folder 171/3)
      - Typescript notes; [3] leaves, Typed on Howard Linday and Russell Crouse letterhead (Box-folder 171/3)
      - Typescript lists for scenes, cast, vignettes, and miscellaneous; [30] leaves, Unbound (Box-folder 171/3)
  - Mizner project or Mizner story see The last resorts and Wise guy
  - More cheers, Unproduced revue, 1934
    - Moon over Napoli, (This is the only song written for More cheers before the show was abandoned. The song was later published and copyrighted for release.)
      - Manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/1)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 172/1)
  - Music box revue, 1921
    - Leather-bound manuscript piano-vocal score; 223 p., Includes typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 172/2)
    - At the court around the corner
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/3)
    - Behind the fan
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/4)
    - Dance of the seasons, Alternate title: Dancing the seasons away
      - Sketch; 2 p., At top: Haig & Keene (performed by Richard W. Keene and Emma Kaig) (Box-folder 172/5)
    - Dance your troubles away
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/6)
    - 8 notes in a scale number(?)
      - Sketch of lead sheet; [3] p. (Box-folder 172/7)
    - Everybody step see also Music box revue, 1938-1939
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/8)
      - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 172/8)
    - I'm a dumbbell
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/9)
    - The legend of the pearls
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/10)
    - My little book of poetry
      - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [6] p. (Box-folder 172/11)
      - Sketch of lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/11)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 172/11)
    - Opening chorus, Includes "What's in the queer-looking bundle?" and "Where am I?"
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/12)
    - The schoolhouse blues
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 172/14)
    - Tell me with a melody, London production ( 1923 ) only
      - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 172/15)
    - They call it dancing see also Music box television spectacular and Non-show music
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/16)
      - Fair copies (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal scores; 4 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 172/16)
    - We work while you sleep, Alternate title: Burglar song
      - Sketch; [4] p. (Box-folder 172/13)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 172/13)
  - Music box revue, 1922
    - Bring on the pepper
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 172/17)
    - Crinoline days
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 172/18)
    - Diamond horseshoe, Alternate title: My diamond horseshoe of girls
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 172/19)
    - I'm looking for a daddy longlegs see Non-show music
    - Lady of the evening
      - Sketch of vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 172/20)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 172/20)
      - Sheet music (Box-folder 172/20)
    - Montmartre see also Music box television spectacular
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/21)
      - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 172/21)
    - Pack up your sins and go to the devil
      - Manuscript piano-vocal scores; [6], 7 p. (Box-folder 172/22)
      - Sketch; [3] p. (Box-folder 172/22)
  - Music box revue, 1923
    - Climbing up the scale
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 173/1)
    - Jazz no.
      - Manuscript full score; 10 p. (Box-folder 173/2)
    - Little butterfly, Alternate title: Butterfly; Chorus melody was used for verse in Home again; 2nd verse is same as verse for Too many sweethearts
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 173/3)
      - Sketches; [16] p. (Box-folder 173/3)
      - Photocopy of printed music; [3] p., With annotations; Found with "Home again" (Box-folder 173/3)
    - One girl
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 173/4)
      - Sketches; [7] p. (Box-folder 173/4)
    - Only a rose, From The vagabond king, music by Rudolf Friml
      - Printed piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 173/5)
    - Opening Act I
      - Manuscript full score; [77] p. (Box-folder 173/6)
    - An orange grove in California
      - Manuscript full score; [8] p. (Box-folder 173/7)
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [5] p. (Box-folder 173/7)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 173/7)
    - Sextette
      - Manuscript full score; [24] p. (Box-folder 173/8)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score and ditto copy; 10 p. each (Box-folder 173/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves, With annotations (Box-folder 173/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 173/8)
      - Manuscript orchestral parts (Box-folder 173/8)
    - Song of the vagabonds, From The vagabond king, music by Rudolf Friml
      - Printed piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 173/9)
    - Venetian Isles see also I'll miss you in the evening
      - Printed piano-vocal score; [4] p., With holograph annotations (Box-folder 173/10)
    - The waltz of long ago, Alternate titles: A waltz of long ago; Waltz song
      - Manuscript full score; 43 p. (Box-folder 173/11)
      - Sketches; [5] p. (Box-folder 173/11)
    - When you walked out, somebody else walked in
      - Fair copies (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal scores (2); 4 p. each (Box-folder 173/12)
  - Music box revue, 1924
    - Alice in Wonderland, Alternate title: Come along with Alice
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 173/13)
      - Photocopy of sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 173/13)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/13)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/13)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 173/13)
    - Bandana ball
      - Sketches; [6] p. (Box-folder 173/14)
      - Manuscript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/14)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 173/14)
    - Broadway scene see Catskill mountains scene
    - The call of the south
      - Manuscript lead sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 173/15)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/15)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/15)
      - Photocopies of typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/15)
      - Sheet music, Without cover (Box-folder 173/15)
    - Catskill mountains scene see also I want to be a ballet dancer, Alternate title: Catskills opening; Includes "Broadway scene," and "Where is my little old New York?"
      - Sketches; [10] p., Includes sketch for "Come to Greenwich Village" (Box-folder 173/16)
      - Photocopies of sketches; [8] p., Lyrics penciled in (Box-folder 173/16)
      - Manuscript and typescript lyric sheets; [12] leaves (Box-folder 173/16)
    - Come to Greenwich Village see Catskill mountain scene
    - A couple of senseless censors, Alternate titles: Censor song; We're a couple of senseless censors
      - Manuscript lyric sheets and program notes; [6] leaves (Box-folder 173/17)
    - Don't send me back to Petrograd, Alternate titles: Don't send me back
      - Manuscript lead sheets(3); [2] p. each (Box-folder 173/18)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/18)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 173/18)
    - Don't wait too long, Used for post-Broadway tour
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 173/19)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 173/19)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 173/19)
    - I want to be a ballet dancer
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., On adjoining page: manuscript lead sheet of "New York" from "Catskill mountain scene"; [1] p.; Laid in: manuscript lyric sheet for "Swanee river" and unidentified sketch; [1] leaf, [1] p. (Box-folder 173/20)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/20)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/20)
    - In the shade of a sheltering tree
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 173/21)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/21)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/21)
      - Photocopy of sheet music, Incomplete (Box-folder 173/21)
    - Listening, Dropped from show
      - Manuscript lead sheets; [1, 2] p., On verso of one page: sketch for "Tell her in the springtime" (Box-folder 173/22)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/22)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 173/22)
    - Rockabye, baby
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 173/23)
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 173/23)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [4] p. (Box-folder 173/23)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 173/23)
    - Tell her in the springtime
      - Photocopy of manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Original is on verso of sketch for Listening (Box-folder 173/24)
      - Manuscript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/24)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/24)
    - Tokyo blues
      - Sketches; [14] p. (Box-folder 173/25)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 173/25)
    - Unlucky in love, Dropped from show
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 173/26)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/26)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 173/26)
    - Where is my little old New York? see Catskill mountains scene
    - Who
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [3] p. (Box-folder 173/27)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/27)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/27)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 173/27)
    - Wild cats, Alternate title: Oh, those wild cats
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 173/28)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 173/28)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 173/28)
    - Yiddisha eskimo see Non-show music
  - Music box revue, 1938-1939, The crystal ball; Unproduced revue
    - Back to back see also Second fiddle
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/1)
    - Commercial photography, Alternate title: In the magazines; Includes the song "Simmons bed"
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 174/3)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 174/3)
    - Columnists' song, Alternate titles: The crystal ball-opening in two scenes; The world is in a mess; See you tomorrow
      - Holograph description of scene and lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 174/4)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves, Includes one page of lyrics for "An old fashioned tune always is new" (Box-folder 174/4)
    - Endorsement song, Alternate title: Celebrity endorsements; In the ads
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 174/2)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 174/2)
    - Everybody step see also Music box revue, 1921
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/5)
    - Hey there, you-manager see Opening-Act III
    - Hitler and Mussolini
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/6)
    - How'd you like what you saw so far? see Opening-Act II
    - I'm a Quaker's daughter from the Latin Quarter see also Non-show music
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/7)
    - I'm sorry for myself see also Second fiddle, Not used
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 174/8)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 174/8)
    - In the early Grecian days see Opening and Opening-Act I
    - It's in three acts instead of the usual two see Opening-Act I
    - Joseph P. Kennedy and prominent American women, Alternate title: We wanted to be present at court, dear Joe
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 174/19)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 174/19)
    - Lost and found bureau
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 174/9)
    - Many are the changes see Opening-Act II
    - Now here is the written endorsement see Endorsement song
    - An old fashioned tune always is new see also Second fiddle
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/10)
    - Opening, Includes "Tickets, please" and "In the early Grecian days"
      - Holograph notes and lyrics; [7] leaves (Box-folder 174/11)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves, Some with annotations (Box-folder 174/11)
    - Opening-Act I (the present, 1939 ), Includes "Tickets, please," "In the early Grecian days," "We know that you first-nighters," "Sherwood, Behrman, Anderson, and Rice," and "It's in three acts instead of the usual two"
      - Holograph description/outlines and lyrics; [12] leaves (Box-folder 174/12)
      - Typescript description/outlines and lyrics; [18] leaves, With holograph notes (Box-folder 174/12)
    - Opening-Act II (the future, 1959), Includes "Many are the changes" and "How'd you like what you saw so far?"
      - Holograph description/outlines and lyrics; [10] leaves (Box-folder 174/13)
      - Typescript description/outlines and lyrics; [9] leaves (Box-folder 174/13)
    - Opening-Act III (the past), Includes "Hey there, you-manager" and "This word-and-music patter"
      - Holograph description/outlines and lyrics; [5] leaves (Box-folder 174/13)
      - Typescript description/outlines and lyrics; [3] leaves (Box-folder 174/13)
    - Patter to Vaudeville show
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves, Found with This is the Army (Box-folder 174/14)
      - Holograph notes; [3] leaves (Box-folder 174/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheets and notes; [16] leaves, With annotations (Box-folder 174/18)
    - Put some clothes on, dear
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/20)
    - Quintuplets' song
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/14)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 174/14)
    - Sherwood, Behrman, Anderson, and Rice see Opening-Act I
    - Simmons bed see Commercial photography
    - Since they turned Loch Lomond into swing see also Carefree
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 174/15)